evri.com 2011-11-26

# Privacy Policy | Evri - Corporate

Last Revised: July 29, 2009

**EVRI.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

**Introduction**

Evri, Inc. (together with its corporate affiliates, collectively, **“Evri”** , **“we”** , or **“us”** ) respects our users’ privacy rights. This policy explains how we may use personal information that you provide to us through and in connection with our websites (including the websites located at http://www.evri.com and http://www.thesummarizer.com) and related services (collectively, the **“Service”** ). We may amend this privacy policy from time to time, including as to specific web sites. If we do so, we will post a revised privacy policy on the Service (or, if only certain site(s) included in the Service are affected, on the affected site(s)), together with a notice of the date it was amended.

**Part I. Information Collection**

You may choose to provide us with information about yourself (including your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, password and other information) that can be used to personally identify you. In addition, our Service may automatically collect certain types of information about you when you use it (such as IP addresses, browser type, browsing history and web site usage information, and information about advertisements and other links that you click on or view).

Any types of information we collect about you that can be used to personally identify you are referred to in this policy collectively as **“Personally Identifiable Information.”** We will never disclose any Personally Identifiable Information related to you to any third party except in the limited circumstances described in this privacy policy.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register an account on the Service or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Service. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@evri.com.

We also employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to help us uniquely identify your computer. Cookies enable Evri to track web site usage patterns and deliver customized content to you. If you wish, you can disable cookies by using the tools provided in your internet browser; however, if you do so, some features of the Service may become unavailable or be limited in their functionality.

Advertisers on the Service and other third parties may also place cookies on your computer, and the Service also contains links to third party web sites. Evri, of course, is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties (including advertisers on the Service or operators of sites linked to from the Service), or for enforcing compliance with them. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of any other web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Evri.

We may also collect information in the course of your interaction with the Service that cannot be used to personally identify you (such as aggregate data regarding web site usage that cannot be specifically tied to any individual, the type of computer and/or operating system you are using, the type of browser you are using and times and dates of usage). This type of information is referred to below as **“Non-Personally Identifying Information.”**

By using the Service, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

**Part II. Information Usage**

We may reproduce, display, transmit, analyze, disclose and otherwise use (and permit third parties to use) Non-Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose, commercial or non-commercial. We may use Personally Identifiable Information: (a) in connection with the operation of the Service; (b) to send you legally required notifications, notifications relating to the operation of the Service, and notifications about features of the Service that you may find interesting, in each case in accordance with your communications preferences set through the Service; and (c) for our internal business purposes.

We will only disclose Personally Identifiable Information about you to third parties in the following circumstances:

(A) If you register an account with us and elect to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information to be publicly associated with your account, we may display that information through the Service in association with your account. Information publicly displayed in your account profile may also be made available to third party search engines.

(B) We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the Service. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the Service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about the Service, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results, advertisements or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Evri-specified purposes.

(C) Certain services and features available through the Service may enable you to post, upload or otherwise make content available, in which you may elect to include Personally Identifiable Information. Please be advised that information posted or otherwise made available through these services or features becomes public knowledge.

(D) We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information when, in our determination, it is legally required under the laws or regulations of any jurisdiction (for example, in response to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process), and when, in our determination, it is necessary to do so to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal or equitable claims;

(E) We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information if we deem it necessary or advisable in order to protect the safety or property of Evri, our users or third parties.

(F) We may let you choose to share Personally Identifiable Information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers.

(G) Certain features or services available through the Service may be provided jointly with other companies. You can tell when another company is involved in any feature or service provided on the Service, and we may share Personally Identifiable Information with that company in connection with your use of that feature or service.

(H) If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Evri business, or individual business units owned by Evri, were to change, your Personally Identifiable Information may be transferred to the new owner so the Service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

**Part III. Access to Information**

If you have created a user profile on the Service, you may modify or delete your profile information by logging into your account. Changes or deletions to profile information will be reflected on the Service immediately. Deleted information may persist in our archives for a reasonable period of time, but will not be generally available to other users. You can also correct or request deletion of any Personally Identifiable Information we store about you by contacting us at [info@evri.com](mailto:info@evri.com).

**Part IV. Data Storage and Security**

Evri uses commercially reasonable technical measures designed to protect our users’ information, including by requesting a unique password to verify your identity before granting you access to any personal account you may have registered with us. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat any security measures we employ, and you acknowledge that you provide your personal information at your own risk. If your Personally Identifiable Information is obtained by a third party as the result of a security breach, and you have provided us with valid contact information, we will notify you promptly after becoming aware of it. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and other credentials used on the Service.

**Part V. Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, and/or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Part VI. Problem Resolution**

If problems arise, or if you have questions about this policy, you may contact us at [info@evri.com](mailto:info@evri.com). You may also contact us by mail at 71 Columbia Street, Ste. 300, Seattle, WA 98104.
